Guide to the New-York Historical Society Portrait Collection circa 1640-2020 (bulk, 1800-1950) PR 52
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Individuals and Family Groups, 59621
  - Subseries I.B. Individuals and Family Groups: Medium Format
    - McGowan, John E. (Drawer Medium)
    - McGrath, J. Howard (Drawer Medium)
    - McKay, Donald, V. (Drawer Medium)
    - McKean, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - McKee, Joseph V. (Drawer Medium)
    - MacKellar, Thomas CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - McKenna, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - McKenzie, D. (Drawer Medium)
    - McKim, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - McKinley, John (Drawer Medium)
    - McKinley, William, and family (2 separate folders) (Drawer Medium)
    - MacLean, Donald (Drawer Medium)
    - McLean, John (Drawer Medium)
    - MacLeod, Donald (Drawer Medium)
    - McKendree, William (Drawer Medium)
    - McNeirny, Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - McPherson, James B. (Drawer Medium)
    - MacPherson, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Machebeuf, Joseph Projectus (Drawer Medium)
    - Mackenzie, Alexander Slidell (Drawer Medium)
    - Macomb, Alexander (Drawer Medium)
    - Macy, J. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Macy, Josiah (Drawer Medium)
    - Madison, James, and Dolley (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Maguire, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Malen, A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Makart, Hans (Drawer Medium)
    - Mangin, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Manning, William J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Mansfield, Erminia Rudersdorff (Drawer Medium)
    - Marconi, Guglielmo (Drawer Medium)
    - Markoe, Francis Jr. CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Marsh, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Marsh, Luther R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Marshall, Charles H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Marshall, George C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Marshall, Humphrey (Drawer Medium)
    - Marshall, John (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Marshall, William R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Martenet, Mrs. Edwin (Drawer Medium)
    - Martin, Augustus Pearl (Drawer Medium)
    - Martin, Charles J. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Marty, Martin (Drawer Medium)
    - Masaccio, Tommaso Aniello (Drawer Medium)
    - Mason (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Mason, A.
      Mason, John M.
      Mason, W. Sanford
    - Massett, Stephen (Drawer Medium)
    - Mather, Cotton (Drawer Medium)
    - Mathewson, Douglas (Drawer Medium)
    - Matthew, Theobald (Drawer Medium)
    - Matthews, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Matthews, Stanley (Drawer Medium)
    - Maurer, Louis (Drawer Medium)
    - Maury, Dabney H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Maverick, Peter (Drawer Medium)
    - Maxey, Samuel Bell (Drawer Medium)
    - May, C. A. (Drawer Medium)
    - May, Homer (Drawer Medium)
    - Mayhew, Ira (Drawer Medium)
    - Mayhew, Jonathan (Drawer Medium)
    - Meade, George G. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Meagher, Thomas Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Mease, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Meckenen, Israel van (Drawer Medium)
    - Meeks, Edwin Bartlett CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Meier, Casper (Drawer Medium)
    - Meigs, Return J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Meir, Golda (Drawer Medium)
    - Meissonier, Jean Louis Ernest (Drawer Medium)
    - Melan, Claude (Drawer Medium)
    - Mellon, Andrew W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Menendez de Aviles, Pedro (Drawer Medium)
    - Mengelberg, Willem (Drawer Medium)
    - Mercer, John Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Mercer, Hugh (Drawer Medium)
    - Mercier (Drawer Medium)
    - Meredith, Solomon (Drawer Medium)
    - Merritt, Wesley (Drawer Medium)
    - Mettler, Samantha (Drawer Medium)
    - Meury, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Michelangelo Buonarroti (Drawer Medium)
    - Mieris, Frans van (Drawer Medium)
    - Mifflin, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Mildeberger, Christopher (Drawer Medium)
    - Miles, Dixon Stansbury (Drawer Medium)
    - Miles, Nelson Appleton (Drawer Medium)
    - Millbank (Drawer Medium)
    - Milledoler, Philip (Drawer Medium)
    - Miller (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Contains
      Miller, Samuel
      Miller, Warner
      Miller, William
    - Millet, Jean-Francois (Drawer Medium)
    - Mills, D. O. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Milton, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Mistral, F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Mitchel, Ormsby MacKnight (Drawer Medium)
    - Mitchell, Alexander (Drawer Medium)
    - Mitchell, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Mitchell, Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Mitchell, Edward P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Mitchell, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Mitchell, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Mitchell, S. Weir (Drawer Medium)
    - Mitchill, Samuel L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Mohn, Marion A. Croll (Drawer Medium)
    - Moliere (Drawer Medium)
    - Moltke, Helmuth, Graf von (Drawer Medium)
    - Monckton, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Monges, J. A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Monnier, Henri (Drawer Medium)
    - Monroe, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Montefiore, Moses (Drawer Medium)
    - Moody, Captain (Drawer Medium)
    - Moody, Dwight L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Moore (Drawer Medium)
    - Moore, Abel Buell (Drawer Medium)
    - Moore, Alfred (Drawer Medium)
    - Moore, Nathaniel F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Moore, Richard Channing (Drawer Medium)
    - Moore, Stephen (Drawer Medium)
    - Mora, Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - More, John, Judge (Drawer Medium)
    - More, John (Drawer Medium)
    - More, Thomas, Sir, Saint (Drawer Medium)
    - Morgan (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Morgan, Daniel
      Morgan, Edwin Dennison
      Morgan, John
      Morgan, John Hunt
      Morgan, John Pierpont
    - Morris (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Morris, George P.
      Morris, Gouvernor
      Morris, Lewis
      Morris, Mary Philipse
      Morris, Robert
      Morris, Roger
      Morris, Samuel P.
    - Morrison, George A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Morse, Samuel F. B., and family (Drawer Medium)
    - Mortimer, Benjamin (Drawer Medium)
    - Morton, John W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Morton, Levi P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Morton, Oliver P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Mosby, John S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Motley, John Lothrop (Drawer Medium)
    - Mott (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Mott, Gersham
      Mott, Lucretia
      Mott, Martha and Caroline
      Mott, Valentine
    - Mowbiery, H. Siddons (Drawer Medium)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus (Drawer Medium)
    - Mullen, Tobias (Drawer Medium)
    - Mulligan, General (Drawer Medium)
    - Munsey, Frank A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Murchison, Roderick Impey, Sir (Drawer Medium)
    - Murger, Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Murillo, Bartolome Esteban (Drawer Medium)
    - Murphey, Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Murray (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Murray, Bronson
      Murray, John
      Murray, Mary Boyles
      Murray, Robert
      Murray, Robert, Mrs.
      Murray, Thomas Archibald
    - Musgrave, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Myers, Louis G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Myers, M. C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Myers, Sally Hecht (Drawer Medium)
    - Napoleon, Emperor (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Nasby, Lock (Drawer Medium)
    - Nast, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Neil, Moses H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Neilson, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Nelson, Horatio, Viscount (Drawer Medium)
    - Nelson, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Nelson, Thomas Jr. (Drawer Medium)
    - Nelson, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Nesbitt, Alexander CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Newbury, I. S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Newman, John H., Cardinal (Drawer Medium)
    - Newmay, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Newton, Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Newton, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Newton, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Ney, le Marechal (Drawer Medium)
    - Niblo, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Nichols, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Nichols, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Nicklin, Julianna (Drawer Medium)
    - Nicoll, Josephine (Drawer Medium)
    - Nicoll, Maud Churchill (Drawer Medium)
    - Ninde, William X. (Drawer Medium)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Nightingale, Florence (Drawer Medium)
    - North, Edward [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - North, Simeon (Drawer Medium)
    - Northcote, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Norton, Mary Louise deWitt (tombstone) (Drawer Medium)
    - Northrop, H. P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Nott, Eliphalet (Drawer Medium)
    - Nye, Jonathan (Drawer Medium)
    - O'Brien, John P. (Drawer Medium)
    - O'Brien, William CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - O'Connell, Daniel (Drawer Medium)
    - O'Conor, Cl. (Drawer Medium)
    - O'Dwyer, Willliam (Drawer Medium)
    - O'Farrell, Michael Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Offen, Benjamin (Drawer Medium)
    - Ogden, Aaron (Drawer Medium)
    - Ogden, James Cochran (Drawer Medium)
    - Ogden, James Kilborn (Drawer Medium)
    - Ogden, Mary Haines (Drawer Medium)
    - Oglesby, R. J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Oglethorpe, James Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Ogilby, John D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Ogilvie, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Onassis, Jacqueline Kennedy (Drawer Medium)
    - Onejero, Tateish (Drawer Medium)
    - O'Neall, Edward A. (Drawer Medium)
    - O'Neill, Henry Patrick CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Opdyke, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Ord, Edward Otho Cresap (Drawer Medium)
    - Ord, Joseph Biays (Drawer Medium)
    - Orr, James L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Orr, S. Alexander (Drawer Medium)
    - O'Ryan, John F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Osborn, Thomas O. (Drawer Medium)
    - Osgood, Sam (Drawer Medium)
    - Osterhaus, Peter Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Oswald, Eleazer (Drawer Medium)
    - Otis, G. S. (Drawer Medium)
    - Otis, J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Ottendorfer, Oswald (Drawer Medium)
    - Otterbern, W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Owen, Joshua Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Owen, Robert Dale (Drawer Medium)
    - Owen, Thomas J. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Paderewski, Ignacy Jan (Drawer Medium)
    - Page, John (b. 1627) (Drawer Medium)
    - Page, John (1800-1850) (Drawer Medium)
    - Page, Mann (Drawer Medium)
    - Paine, Halbert E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Paine, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Paine, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Palmer (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Palmer, B. M.
      Palmer, Erastus Dow
      Palmer, Fanny
      Palmer, Innis Newton
      Palmer, William Pitt
    - Palmerston, Henry John Temple (Drawer Medium)
    - Panmure, William Maule, Earl of (Drawer Medium)
    - Parke, John G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Parker, Abel (Drawer Medium)
    - Parker, Amos J. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Parker, Ely Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Parker, Theodore (Drawer Medium)
    - Parkman, Francis (Drawer Medium)
    - Paris, Henri, comte de (Drawer Medium)
    - Parish, Edward C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Parish, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Parmly, Charles Howard (Drawer Medium)
    - Parrish, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Parris, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Parsons, Usher (Drawer Medium)
    - Pastoret, Claude Emmanuel Joseph Pierre, marquis de (Drawer Medium)
    - Pasteur, Louis (Drawer Medium)
    - Patchen, Jacob (Drawer Medium)
    - Paterson, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Patrick, Marsena Rudolph (Drawer Medium)
    - Patterson, Henry Stuart (Drawer Medium)
    - Patterson, Martha (Drawer Medium)
    - Patterson, Robert (1792-1881) (Drawer Medium)
    - Patterson, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Patterson, Robert M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Patterson, Robert U. (Drawer Medium)
    - Patton, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Paul, Gabriel R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Paulding, Hiram (Drawer Medium)
    - Paulding, James K. (Drawer Medium)
    - Paulding, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Paulding, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Payne, John Howard (Drawer Medium)
    - Payne, N. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Peabody, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Peale, Rembrandt (Drawer Medium)
    - Peary, Robert E. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Pease, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Peckham, Wheeler Hazard (Drawer Medium)
    - Pegram, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Pelham, Jonathan (Drawer Medium)
    - Pemberton, J. C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Pence, N. B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Pendleton, George H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Pendleton, W. N. (Drawer Medium)
    - Penfield, Frederic C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Penn, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Penn, John (1700-1746) (Drawer Medium)
    - Pennell, Calliope (Drawer Medium)
    - Pennell, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Pennington, Alexander C. M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Pennington, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Pepperrell, Lady (Drawer Medium)
    - Pepperrell, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Perham, Sidney (Drawer Medium)
    - Perris, William G. (Drawer Medium)
    - Perry (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Perry, A. J.
      Perry, Edward Aylesworth
      Perry, Eli
      Perry, I. A.
      Perry, John
      Perry, Matthew C.
      Perry, Oliver
    - Pershing, John J. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Petain, Henri Phillippe Omer (Drawer Medium)
    - Peters, Richard (1704-1776) (Drawer Medium)
    - Peters, Richard (1744-1828) (Drawer Medium)
    - Pettengill, Samuel M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Pettigrew, J. Johnston (Drawer Medium)
    - Pettit, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Peyton, John Rowzee (Drawer Medium)
    - Phelps, Amos A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Phelps, Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Phelps, E. J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Phelps, J. J. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Phelps, Royal [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Philip, John W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Philips, Wendell (Drawer Medium)
    - Phillips, Jame [James?] L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Phillips, W. W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Phoenix, Daniel (Drawer Medium)
    - Phoenix, S. Whiting (Drawer Medium)
    - Pickering, T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Pickett, George E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Pickhardt, William Paul (Drawer Medium)
    - Pier, Rufus (Drawer Medium)
    - Pierce, Byron R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Pierce, Franklin (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Pierce, Palmer E. (Drawer Medium)
    - Pierpont (Drawer Medium)
    - Pierre, T. B. M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Pierrepont, Edwards (Drawer Medium)
    - Pierrepont, Henry E. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Pike, Albert (Drawer Medium)
    - Pike, Zebulon M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Pillow, Gideon Johnson (Drawer Medium)
    - Pinckney, Charles Colesworth (Drawer Medium)
    - Pinckney, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Pinkney, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Pintard, John, and Brasher, Elizabeth (Drawer Medium)
    - Pitman, Harriet Minot (Drawer Medium)
    - Pitt, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Pius IX, Pope (Drawer Medium)
    - Pius X, Pope (Drawer Medium)
    - Pius XI, Pope (Drawer Medium)
    - Plater, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Platt, T. C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Playfair, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Pleasanton, Alfred (Drawer Medium)
    - Plumsted, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Poe, Edgar Allan (Drawer Medium)
    - Poincare, M. Raymond (Drawer Medium)
    - Poinsett, Joel Roberts (Drawer Medium)
    - Polk, James K., and wife (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Polk, Leonidas (Drawer Medium)
    - Polk, Lucius Eugene (Drawer Medium)
    - Pomeroy, Samuel Clarke (Drawer Medium)
    - Pomeroy, Theodore M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Pompadour, Jeanne Antoinette Poisson, marquise de (Drawer Medium)
    - Poole, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Poor, Enoch (Drawer Medium)
    - Pope, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Porter, David (Drawer Medium)
    - Porter, David D. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Porter, David R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Porter, Fitz John (Drawer Medium)
    - Porter, James Madison (Drawer Medium)
    - Porter, William D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Posey, Carnot (Drawer Medium)
    - Post, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Potter, Alonzo (Drawer Medium)
    - Potter, Clarkson N. (Drawer Medium)
    - Potter, Henry Codman [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Potter, Horatio [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Potter, Paul (Drawer Medium)
    - Potter, Robert P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Poussin, Nicholas (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Powell, L. L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Powell, W. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Powers, Hiram (Drawer Medium)
    - Pownall, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Pratt, Benjamin (Drawer Medium)
    - Pratt, Zadock (Drawer Medium)
    - Prentice (Drawer Medium)
    - Prentice, George D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Prentice, J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Prentiss, Benjamin Maybarry (Drawer Medium)
    - Prescott, Henry A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Prescott, William Hickling (Drawer Medium)
    - Preston, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Price, Richard (Drawer Medium)
    - Price, Richard Butler (Drawer Medium)
    - Price, Rodman M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Price, Sterling (Drawer Medium)
    - Priestley, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Prince, William C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Provost, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Pugh, Sarah (Drawer Medium)
    - Pulitzer, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Pullman, John Wesley CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Pullman, Lewis (Drawer Medium)
    - Purple, Samuel Smith (Drawer Medium)
    - Putnam, George Haven (Drawer Medium)
    - Putnam, George P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Putnam, Israel (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Putnam, Tarrant (Drawer Medium)
    - Putnam, William Lowell (Drawer Medium)
    - Pynaker, Adam (Drawer Medium)
    - Quanbill, William Clark (Drawer Medium)
    - Quezon, Manuel Luis (Drawer Medium)
    - Quintard, C. J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Quitman, John A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Raguet, Condy (Drawer Medium)
    - Raimondi, Marcantonio (Drawer Medium)
    - Rains, Gabriel James (Drawer Medium)
    - Rafinesque, Constantine Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Ramsay, Nat (Drawer Medium)
    - Ramseur, Stephen (Drawer Medium)
    - Rand, Charles Frederic (Drawer Medium)
    - Randall, S. S., and Family (Drawer Medium)
    - Randall, Samuel Sidwell (Drawer Medium)
    - Randolph, Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Randolph, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Ranft, Otto Richard (Drawer Medium)
    - Ranger, Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Rankin, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Rankin, John Walker (Drawer Medium)
    - Raphael (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Ratcliff, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Raven, Anton A. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Rawlins, John A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Rawolle, Frederick CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Ray, Robert [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Raymond, Henry J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Read, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Read, Meredith (Drawer Medium)
    - Read, Thomas Buchanan (Drawer Medium)
    - Reagan, James H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Redpath, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Reed, Hugh B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Reed, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Reed, Luman (Drawer Medium)
    - Reed, Thomas B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Reich, William C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Reid, John Morrison (Drawer Medium)
    - Rembrandt Harmenszoon van Rijn (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Remond, Charles Lenox (Drawer Medium)
    - Reno, Jesse L. (Drawer Medium)
    - Revere, Paul (Drawer Medium)
    - Reynald (Drawer Medium)
    - Reynolds (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Reynolds, Jane, Countess of Harrington
      Reynolds, John Fulton
      Reynolds, Joseph S.
      Reynolds, Joshua
    - Rhett, J. Barnwell (Drawer Medium)
    - Rhodes, E. H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Rhodes, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Rice, Elliott W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Rice, James C. (Drawer Medium)
    - Rice, Samuel A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Richards, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Richards, George, Mrs. (Drawer Medium)
    - Richards, Mary M. Bullard (tombstone) (Drawer Medium)
    - Richardson, Albert B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Richardson, Israel Bush (Drawer Medium)
    - Ricketts, James B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Ricketts, R. Bruce (Drawer Medium)
    - Ridgaway, Henry Bascom (Drawer Medium)
    - Riker, Richard (Drawer Medium)
    - Ringgold, Cadwalader (Drawer Medium)
    - Ringgold, Samuel (Drawer Medium)
    - Riordan, D. M. (Drawer Medium)
    - Ritter, Jacob, Jr. (Drawer Medium)
    - Ritzema, Joannes (Drawer Medium)
    - Rivington, James (Drawer Medium)
    - Roach, Isaac (Drawer Medium)
    - Roach, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Robbins, Thomas (Drawer Medium)
    - Roberts, G. T. (Drawer Medium)
    - Roberts, George W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Roberts, John Sinclair CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Roberts, Joseph (Drawer Medium)
    - Robertson (Drawer Medium)
    - Robertson, Archibald (Drawer Medium)
    - Robertson, Beverly Holcombe (Drawer Medium)
    - Robertson, Jerome Bonaparte (Drawer Medium)
    - Robinson (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Robinson, Mrs.
      Robinson, Beverley
      Robinson, Fanny De Groot & Francis Isabel
      Robinson, James Fisher
      Robinson, John Cleveland
      Robinson, M. N.
    - Rochambeau, Jean-Baptiste Donatien, de (Drawer Medium)
    - Rockefeller, John D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Roddey, Philip Dale (Drawer Medium)
    - Rodman, Isaac P. (Drawer Medium)
    - Rodney, Caesar (Drawer Medium)
    - Roebling, John Augustus (Drawer Medium)
    - Roebuck, John Arthur (Drawer Medium)
    - Rogers, Horatio Jr. (Drawer Medium)
    - Rogers, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Rogers, N. D. (Drawer Medium)
    - Rogers, Randolph (Drawer Medium)
    - Rogers, Robert (Drawer Medium)
    - Roland, Hyacinthe Gabrielle (Drawer Medium)
    - Rolston, Roswell G. [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Romain, Jules (Drawer Medium)
    - Romeyn, J. B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Romney, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Rook, Logan H. (Drawer Medium)
    - Roorbach, Orville Augustus (Drawer Medium)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, and family (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Roosevelt, R. B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore (1831-1878) [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Roosevelt, Theodore (1858-1919) (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      General and Family (2 folders)
      Memorials
      Military
    - Root, Adrian R. (Drawer Medium)
    - Rosecrans, William Starke (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Rosenthal, Albert (Drawer Medium)
    - Rosenthal, Max (Drawer Medium)
    - Rosinof, Vladimir (Drawer Medium)
    - Ross, Isabella Clark (Drawer Medium)
    - Rosser, Thomas Lafayette (Drawer Medium)
    - Rothermel, Peter Frederick (Drawer Medium)
    - Rouss (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
      Rouss, Charles Balzell
      Rouss, Peter Winchester
      Rouss, William Washington
    - Rousseau, Lovell Harrison (Drawer Medium)
    - Rowe, D. Watson (Drawer Medium)
    - Rowland, Henry A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Rubens, Peter Paul, and Helene Fourment Rubens (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Ruge, Herman Arnold (Drawer Medium)
    - Ruggles, Daniel (Drawer Medium)
    - Ruggles, S. B. (Drawer Medium)
    - Rush, Benjamin (Drawer Medium)
    - Rush, William (Drawer Medium)
    - Rusk, Jeremiah McLean (Drawer Medium)
    - Rusk, Richard (Drawer Medium)
    - Ruskin, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Russell, John Russell, Earl (Drawer Medium)
    - Russell, S. A. (Drawer Medium)
    - Rutgers, Henry (Drawer Medium)
    - Rutledge, Edward (Drawer Medium)
    - Rutledge, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Ryan, James (Drawer Medium)
    - St. Clair, Arthur (Drawer Medium)
    - St. Clair, John (Drawer Medium)
    - Saint-Gaudens, Augustus (Drawer Medium)
    - St. John de Crevecoeur, J. Hector (Drawer Medium)
    - St. Leger, Barry (Drawer Medium)
    - Saint Memin, Charles Balthazar Julien Fevre de (Drawer Medium)
    - Saint-Vallier, Jean-Baptiste de la Croix de Chevriáeres de (Drawer Medium)
    - Sabin, Joseph F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Sackett, Nathaniel (Drawer Medium)
    - Sage, Henry Williams [crossed out] (Drawer Medium)
    - Salisbury, Robert Gascoyne-Cecil, Marquess of (Drawer Medium)
    - Salvatierra, Jose Ines (Drawer Medium)
    - Sampson, William T. (separate folder) (Drawer Medium)
    - Samson, George W. (Drawer Medium)
    - Sand, George (Drawer Medium)
    - Sandby, Paul (Drawer Medium)
    - Sanderson, J. (Drawer Medium)
    - Sands, Comfort (Drawer Medium)
    - Sands, Robert Charles (Drawer Medium)
    - Sands, Walter Seabury CCNY (Drawer Medium)
    - Sandy, B. F. (Drawer Medium)
    - Sansovino, Giacomo (Drawer Medium)
    - Saracco (Drawer Medium)
    - Sargent, Henrietta (Drawer Medium)